A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 2 FA1440
Rockefeller Archive Center
Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 2
1950-1985
Rockefeller Archive Center
Agricultural Development Council
Rockefeller, John D., III (John Davison) (1906-1978)
FA1440
134.22 Cubic Feet 285 containers
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Biographical / Historical
The Agricultural Development Council was founded in 1953 by John D. Rockefeller 3rd as the Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs, Inc. It was incorporated as a private, nonprofit organization under the laws of the state of New York.
In 1963, the name was changed, but the purpose and objectives remained unchanged from those stated in the original certificate of incorporation. In broad terms these are "charitable, scientific and educational and are designed to stimulate and support economic and related activities important to human welfare".
The Council, from its inception committed a major part of its resources and its staff to training and research activities in social science fields. These activities followed both formal and informal patterns, with a single aim, to strengthen professional capacity to deal with the economic and human problems of agricultural and rural development in Asia.
In 1985 the Council merged with two other Rockefeller-related agricultural programs, the Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center and the Rockefeller Foundation's International Agricultural Development Service to create the Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development.
Arrangement
Arranged in 14 series by file type. Records remain physically in order as received.
Scope and Contents
Record Group 2 of the Agricultural Development Council collection primarily contains Fellowship files, administrative records of the Fellowship Program, Core Program files, records of both the Regional Research and Training Program (RRTP) and the Research and Training Network (RTN) as well as conference, seminar and workshop files and papers. Of particular note, there is also a small volume of Board of Trustees files and Field Office Staff reports.
Agriculture; Agricultural education; Public welfare; Agricultural systems -- Developing countries; Economic development; Farm management; Agronomy; Asia
- Fellows Files, 1950-1985; 1; 24.31 Cubic Feet 64 letter document boxes
  - India, 1.1
    - Tara N. Patel, 1966-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Surya M. Pathak, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bhivarao Radjhar Patil, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Vaithilingim Rajagopalan, 1958-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Revanna Ramanna, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Ranga K. Rao, 1966-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Musunuru Rao, 1967-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Paramahansa Ray, 1955-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Hardial Singh Saini, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Tara C. Shukla, 1967-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Abdur Rashid Siddiqi, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - B. N. Singh, 1959-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Devendra K. Singh, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Hakim Singh, 1959-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Raghbir Singh, 1963-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Ragubar Singh, 1962-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Mohammad Sultan, 1950-1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - S. B. Tambad, 1960-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Augustine D. Wycliffe, 1955-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Mahesh C. Agarwal, 1956-1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Babu Lal Agarwal, 1955-1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - B. V. S. Baliga, 1960-1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Herbert W. Butt, 1956-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - John B. Chitambar, 1967-1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Dhirajlal K. Desai, 1957-1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - P. N. Driver, 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Mahendra P. Gupta, 1961-1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Satish Chandra Jha, 1958-1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - M. J. John, 1962-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Raj Krishna, 1958-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Sudha S. Lall, 1962-1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Manoranjan Majumdar, 1965-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Harbans Singh Mann, 1958-1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - T. V. Moorti, 1962-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Santosh Kumar Pain, 1955-1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - J. V. Venkataram, 1968-1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Govind Khudanpur, 1958-1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Chaganti Ravindra Prasad Rao (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Tej Pratap Singh, 1964-1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Siddanaik Bisaliah, 1970-1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Bangladesh, 1.2
    - Shansul Islam, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Salauddin Md. Nural Alam, 1972-1983 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Burma, 1.3
    - Maung Maung Htwe, 1964-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Kyaw Myint, 1965-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia, 1.4
    - Saleh Afiff, 1963-1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Achmad T. Birowo, 1960-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Tohir Kaslan, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - E. Roekasah Adiratma, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Sie Kwat Soen Sabudiahih, 1957-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Achmad Soeharjo, 1966-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Igusti Bagus Teken, 1963-1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bungaran Saragih, 1974-1980 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Irlan Soejono, 1969-1977 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Ismet Ahmad, 1976-1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Wirjadi Prawirodihardjo, 1970-1974 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Alhambra Rachman, 1968-1974 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Rudolf S. Sinaga, 1967-1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Soetatwo S. Hadiwigeno, 1969-1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Ahmad Sjamsuddin Surjana, 1972-1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Tuhpawana Priatna Sendjaja, 1974-1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Affendi Anwar, 1969-1974 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Thamrin Nurdin, 1969-1977 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Margono Slamet, 1961-1977 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Sjarifuddin Baharsjah, 1968-1980 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - John J. O. I. Ihalauw, 1973-1979 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - M. Umar Burhan, 1976-1980 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Muhammad Amin Aziz, 1966-1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Harbrinderjit Singh Dillon, 1975-1983 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Japan, 1.5
    - Tyoji Abe, 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Kenji Cho, 1962-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Minoru Fukuda, 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Kenichi Hayashi, 1965-1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Toshihiko Isobe, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Kurashiro Isumi, 1957-1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Isowo Iwakata, 1957-1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Kunio Kagayama, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Masashi K. Kambe, 1959-1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Natsuki Kanazawa, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hirochika Kanzaki, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Takahi Kasegawa, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Yuzuru Kato, 1957-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Shohei Kawakatsu, 1955-1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Shoji Kayashima, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Taiji Kikuchi, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Yoshiharu Kubo, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Zyuro Kudo, 1965-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Toshio Kuroyanasi, 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Masanobu Kuwahara, 1957-1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Yoshihiro Maruyama, 1961-1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Yukio Masui, 1962-1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Toshiro Matsuda, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Sakujiro Momono, 1958-1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Hiroshi Mori, 1958-1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Takeshi Motooka, 1957-1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Shizuo Murayama, 1959-1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kazuo Muto, 1961-1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Shosuke Nakamura, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Ichiro Nishigaki, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Hiroyuki Nishimura, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Takuji Sakurai, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Juichi Sato, 1958-1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Shujiro Sawada, 1961-1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Seiji Shindo, 1961-1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Masashi Shono, 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Sachiko Y. Sidhu, 1964-1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Fukumatsu Suzuki, 1961-1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Tsuneo Suzuki, 1958-1965 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Iichiro Takahashi, 1955-1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Tadashi Tenma, 1958-1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Takashi Takayama, 1955-1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Keizo Tsuchiya, 1963-1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Fukuo Ueno, 1957-1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Shigeyoshi Ueno, 1961-1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Toshimi Umeki, 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Takeshi Yajima, 1955-1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Osamu Yamamoto, 1959-1961 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Taira Yori, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Malaysia, 1.6
    - Abdul Aziz bin Yahaya, 1968-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Abdullah bin Ujang, 1964-1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Collin E. R. Abraham, 1967-1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Abu Bakar bin Mahmud, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Mohd Sheffie Bakar, 1968-1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Ch'ng How Soo, 1964-1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Chung Choeng Hoy, 1966-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Harun Derauh, 1967-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Ishak bin Tadin, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Swee Joo Khoo, 1963-1967 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Nik Hashim, 1968-1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Agoes Salim, 1961-1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Isher Singh Sekhon, 1965-1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Rahmat Suffian, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Tang Loon Boon, 1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Ti Teow Choo, 1968-1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Wahab Alwi, 1967-1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Afifuddin bin Haji Omar, 1968-1979 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Chew Tek Ann, 1969-1979 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Jegatheesan Shanmugam, 1971-1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Loke Keng Hung, 1970-1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Mokhtar bin Tamin, 1964-1979 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Mohammed Ariff bin Hussein, 1970-1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Radzuan bin Abdul Rahman, 1968-1980 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Anthony J. Reutens, 1969-1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Mohd. Rosli bin Abdul Aziz (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - William Wong Yen, 1968-1977 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Tan Bock Thiam, 1965-1977 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Yeoh Oon Lee, 1966-1977 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Wan Leong Fee, 1969-1977 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Pakistan, 1.7
    - Nafis Ahmad, 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Mirza Amjad Ali Beg, 1962-1972 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Muhammad Ghaffar Chaudhry, 1968-1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Chaudry Inayatullah, 1963-1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Riaz Ahmad Khan, 1960-1977 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Muhammad Iqbal Malik, 1957-1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Akhter Mohyuddin, 1959-1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Ijaz Ahmad Qumar, 1963-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - A. I. H. Rizvi, 1958-1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Saiyed M. H. Rizvi, 1965-1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Sultan Saghir Ahmad, 1960-1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Abdul Jameel Siddiqi, 1962-1966 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Asif Raza, 1973-1980 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Philippines, 1.8
    - Ernesto P. Abarientos (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Jose V. Abueva (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Dora S. Ackerman (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Valentino C. Alipio (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Wilfredo F. Arce (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Eric S. Casino (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Dalmacio A. Cruz (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Leopoldo P. de Guzman (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Basilio N. de los Reyes (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Sylvia H. Guerrero (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Jose M. Lawas (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Oscar J. S. Lazo (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Priscila S. Manalang (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Alejandro A. Maralit (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Eulalio G. Maturan (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Rogelio P. Megino (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Lilia C. Panganiban (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Leonardo A. Paulino (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Emilio U. Quintana (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Vincente A. Quiton (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Orlando J. Sacay (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Pedro R. Sandoval (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Catalina D. Shea (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Santiago S. Simpas (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Jesus C. Sta. Iglesia (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Nathaniel B. Tablante (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Pablo T. Tapia (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Rufino G. Tima (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Fabian A. Tiongson (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Enriqueta Bernal Torres (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Levy A. Trinidad, 1962-1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Perla Togumpay Umale, 1962-1966 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Buenaventura M. Villanueva, 1958-1965 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Patrocinio Santos Villanueva, 1956-1979 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Alberto Abu Virtuosi, 1963-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Teresita T. Voelkner, 1960-1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Gloria V. Yap, 1955-1957 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Mario D. Zamora, 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Cayetano S. Sarmago (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Severino B. Vergara, 1975-1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Leila C. Ilan, 1975-1980 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Mauricio D. Leonor, Jr., 1970-1978 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Raymundo E. Fonollera, 1966-1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Jaime B. Valera, 1974-1979 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Jerome F. Sison, 1976-1982 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Cynthia S. Bantilan, 1976-1984 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Elizabeth M. King, 1976-1982 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Marietta S. Adriano, 1974-1980 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Donato B. Antiporta, 1960-1980 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Carl B. Montano, 1973-1980 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Narciso M. Mindajao, 1973-1978 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Victoria A. Bautista, 1971-1979 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Florentino Librero, 1962-1979 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Teresa J. Ho, 1975-1980 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Eduardo S. Canlas, 1972-1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Helen A. Cruz, 1967-1980 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Singapore, 1.9
    - Francis Kwong Wah Chan, 1963-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Augustine H. H. Tan, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - South Korea, 1.10
    - Sung Hwan Ban, 1960-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Dong Sup Chang, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Hung Bok Chin, 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Sung Ji Cho, 1963-1969 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Kyoo Soo Han, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Dong Hi Kim, 1962-1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Ho Tak Kim, 1965-1979 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Il Chul Kim, 1964-1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Sung-Hoon Kim, 1965-1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Jong Yeul Kong, 1964-1979 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chun Sur Koo, 1961-1978 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Teck Chin Kwon, 1964-1979 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Jil Hyun Lee, 1964-1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Jae Woon Moon, 1967-1979 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Pal Yong Moon, 1967-1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Hong Nai Park, 1962-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Jin Hwan Park, 1960-1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Jae Han Rhee, 1961-1980 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - Young Kun Shim, 1963-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Hae Kyun Song, 1965-1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Joong Il Suh, 1964-1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - In Keun Wang, 1959-1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Choe Yang Boo, 1970-1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Jeung Han Lee, 1967-1980 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Chul Ho Yoo, 1973-1982 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Sri Lanka, 1.11
    - Thambapillai Jogaratnam (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Guy Motha, 1967-1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Upali Nanayakkara, 1968-1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - S. N. Samuel, 1964-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - S. T. Senewiratne, 1964-1974 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Annesley P. A. Fernando, 1969-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Seyedaham M. F. Marikar, 1973-1980 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Nimal E. H. Sanderatine, 1969-1980 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Sathyapala Pinnaduwage, 1969-1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan, 1.12
    - Jin-Yuk Chang, 1962-1969 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Te Tsui Chang, 1960-1967 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Ching-yuan Chao, 1958-1972 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Chao-chen Chen, 1956-1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Chen Chin-Wen, 1961-1967 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Hsing-yiu Chen, 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Lin-Tsang Chen, 1962-1970 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Frederick Chi-tso Chou, 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Charles Chwei-lin Fan, 1957-1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Shuh Ching Fan, 1955-1973 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Pi-Feng Hong, 1967-1972 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Sam-Chung Hsieh, 1956-1979 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Wen-fu Hsu, 1958-1978 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Yu Chu Hsu, 1960-1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Chi-Lien Huang, 1957-1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Kuo-shiung Huang, 1964-1979 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Min-shioh Kwoh, 1967-1978 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Weng-chieh Lai, 1963-1972 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Ching Yu Lee, 1963-1967 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Paul Shen-Tung Lee, 1962-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Teng-hui Lee, 1963-1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Tsoung-Chao Lee, 1962-1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Peter C. Lin, 1962-1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Yu-Kang Mao, 1960-1973 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Peter Po-Chuan Sun, 1961-1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Chieh-Hsin Tseng, 1962-1977 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Young-Chi Tsui (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - James C. W. Wang, 1959-1979 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Te-hsing Wang, 1958-1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - You-Tsao Wang, 1955-1972 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Terry Yu-Hsien Yu, 1961-1972 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Shun-cheng Lee, 1975-1982 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Thailand, 1.13
    - Arb Nakajud (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Bimbardha Sirivongse Na Ayudhya (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Supanee M. Artachinda, 1967-1971 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Bantorn Ondam, 1967-1973 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Chaiwat Konjing, 1967-1975 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Chamnien Boonma, 1967-1972 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Chanond Aranyakananda, 1963-1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Dhanomkulbutra Choonwongse, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Manu Seetisarn, 1960-1968 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Kamphol Adulavidhaya, 1960-1969 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Marnop Debhavalya, 1954-1977 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Paitoon Cruagao, 1959-1979 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Pantum Thisyamondol, 1959-1970 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Pradit Charsombuti, 1967-1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Prasit Swasyart, 1967-1970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Radom Setteeton, 1962-1967 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Sopin Tongpan, 1961-1969 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Suphan Tosunthorn, 1962-1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Padh Tavaranusorn, 1958-1968 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Thiravet Pramuanratkarn, 1967-1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Tongruay Chungtes, 1964-1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Virach Arromdee, 1963-1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Udom Kerdpibule, 1964-1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Wirat Intrachooto, 1962-1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - CECA Fellows, 1954-1963 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Apisith Issariyanukula, 1975-1981 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Boontham Chitana, 1969-1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Koset Manowalailao, 1972-1979 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Narong Srisawas, 1970-1980 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Pairat Decharin, 1973-1980 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Saroj Aungsumalin, 1974-1982 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Vivat Shotelersuk, 1970-1979 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Titaya Suvanajata, 1969-1979 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Pote Boonruang, 1967-1979 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Rapeepun Sektheera, 1974-1979 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Sarun Wattanutchariya, 1972-1981 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Arkom Soothipan, 1969-1971 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Bhochana Panyadhibya Punyatip, 1955-1960 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - South Vietnam, 1.14
    - Truong Quang Canh, 1967-1984 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Nepal, 1.15
    - Binayak Prasad Bhadra, 1976-1981 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bekha Lal Maharajan, 1969-1979 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Som Prasad Pudasaini, 1976-1982 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Vijaya Shrestha, 1975-1980 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Durgesh Man Singh Shrestha, 1979-1985 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Devendra Prasad Chapagain, 1978-1984 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Fellowship Program Administration, 1955-1981; 2; 8.62 Cubic Feet 20 containers
  - Fellowship Committee Meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
  - Fellowship Committee Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 1-5)
  - Fellowship Committee Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 1-6)
  - Fellowship Committee Meetings, 1970-1972 (Box 67, Folder 1-5)
  - Fellowship Committee Meetings, 1972-1974 (Box 68, Folder 1-5)
  - Fellowship Committee Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 69, Folder 1-5)
  - Asian Fellowship Program Manual, 1981 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship Committee Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 132, Folder 2-7)
  - Fellowship Committee Meeting, 1980 May 6 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Fellows - General, 1957-1966 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Fellows - General, 1958-1980 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Non-degree Fellowships, 1977-1978 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Administration - General, 1976-1977 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Reports and Administration - Thailand, 1962-1979 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Reports and Administration - South Korea, 1969-1976 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Reports and Administration - Sri Lanka, 1967-1978 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Reports and Administration - Taiwan, 1962-1979 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Reports and Administration - Nepal, 1971-1980 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Administration - Pakistan, 1957-1979 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Reports and Administration - Philippines, 1958-1979 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Reports and Administration - Indonesia, 1957-1980 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Reports and Administration - Japan, 1965-1977 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Reports and Administration - Malaysia, 1959-1979 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Reports and Administration - India, 1957-1978 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Administration - Bangladesh, 1975-1980 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Directory of Fellows Preparation, 1966, 1968, 1970, 1973, 1976, 1966-1976 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - ADC Conference of Fellows, College Park, MD, 1966 August (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Conference of Indian Fellows, New Delhi, 1967 March 18-20 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - ADC Conference of Fellows, Bozeman, MT, 1968 August (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - ADC Conference of Fellows, Columbia, Missouri, 1970 August (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - ADC Conference of Fellows, Gainsville, FL, 1972 August (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - ADC Conference of Fellows, College Station, TX, 1974 August (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - ADC Conference of Fellows, University Park, PA, 1976 August (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Land Policy Course, Wisconsin, 1972 June 19-July 4 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Staff Conferences - Fellowship Discussion, 1967; 1974-1979 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship Questionnaires (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - ARS - Graduate Study Booklet, Revised 1975, 1974-1976 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE) - Administration of ADC Fellowship Program, 1955-1966 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - East West Center, 1963-1971 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - English and Orientation Programs (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Fellowship Program Forms, Record-Keeping materials, Publications, 1960s-1970s (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Bangladesh - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - India - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Malaysia - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Nepal - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Philippines - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - South Korea - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Tawain - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Thailand - Rejected or Approved-Cancelled-Withdrawn, 1970s (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - U. S. and Asian Fellowship Programs - Financial Ledgers, 1968-1981 (Box 76)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Confidential material
  - U. S. and Asian Fellowship Programs - Vouchers, 1968-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1-5)
  - U. S. and Asian Fellowship Programs - Vouchers, 1968-1979 (Box 78, Folder 1-5)
  - U. S. and Asian Fellowship Programs - Vouchers, 1968-1979 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)